Oneida Community Collection
Oneida Community Collection
- Manuscripts and personal papers
  - Noyes, Horatio Temple, 1872; 1887 (Box 67)
    1872 N 22 to [Fidelia Dunn]
    1887 O 17 to 'Dear Cousin'
  - Noyes, John Humphrey, 1831-1885; undated
    See also Guiteau, Charles
    - Correspondence, 1831-1880 (Box 68)
      1831 S 29 to Larkin G. Mead
      1838 Ap 4 to Jonathan Burt
      1850 O 31 Manlius affairs'
      1852 Ap 4 to Larkin G. Mead
      Ap 19 to Brother Burnham
      1855 F 13 to Harriet Worden
      1857 D 25 Christmas greeting to 'Annie'
      1861 F 17 to James B. Herrick
      N 20 to Marcus L. Worden
      1863 Ap 4 to Charles S. Joslyn
      1864 D 28 to Gerrit Smith (copy; original in Syracuse University's Gerrit Smith Coll.)
      1866 Je 20 to Beulah
      1867 My 16 to George Washington Noyes
      My 21 to Mary Louise Prindle
      My 28 to Hepworth Dixon
      1868 Ja 11 to Marcus L. Worden
      1869 F 26 to George Washington Noyes in T.C. Miller file (3-28-1869)
      Je 16 to Tirzah C. Miller(?) with Je 17 1869 on verso
      1870 Ap 30 to Charlotte A. Miller -- with Charlotte A. Miller's reply
      Je 29 to George H. Burnham -- in G.H. Burnham file
      Ag 24 to R.D. Pease (copy; original in N.Y. State Library)
      1871 F 7 to William A. Hinds
      Mr 10 to James B. Herrick
      My 2 to Harriet H. Skinner
      1874 Ja 30 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 21 to Alfred Barron
      1875 Ja 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ja to Harriet H. Skinner
      Ja 23 to Tirzah C. Miller
      F 6 to Tirzah C. Miller
      F 25 to James B. Herrick
      Ap 1 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 21 to Humphrey
      1876 to Beulah
      Mr 5 to Charles Nordhoff (copy; original in Massachusetts Historical Society)
      Mr 8 to William A. Hinds
      Mr 10 to William A. Hinds
      Ap 15 to William A. Hinds
      Jl 8 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Jl 17 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Jl 31 to ? about Tirzah C. Miller
      Ag 9 telegram to Charles A. Cragin
      Ag 17 to William A. Hinds?
      N 12 to Alfred Barron
      1877 Ja 20 to William A. Hinds
      Mr 4 to William A. Hinds
      Mr 31 to 'Dear H'
      Je to Edward P. Inslee (for W.H. Woolworth's signature)
      S 15 to John B. Niles (copy; original in Lilly Library, Indiana University)
      1878 Mr 25 to Abel Easton
      Mr 29 to Abel Easton
      Ap 12 to Abel Easton
      Ap 16 to Abel Easton
      My 5 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Je 2 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 14 to Theodore L. Pitt
      Je 17 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 18 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Je 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 20 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 21 Covenant between John Humphrey Noyes and Tirzah C. Miller re: Edward P. Inslee
      Jl 20 to John Norton
      Jl 24 to Tirzah C. Miller -- in T.C. Miller file
      1879 Mr 28 to Mary Louise Prindle
      My 10 to Abel Easton
      My 14 to Abel Easton
      My 21 note -- in Abel Easton file
      Je 18 to Abel Easton
      O to James B. Herrick
      1880 Ja 23 to 'Council and Family'
      F 27 to Harriet H. Skinner--with note from Harriet A. Noyes to Harriet H. Skinner
      Ap 15 to Edmund Burke
      O 27 to Harriet Skinner
      N 9 'Covenant of Peace'
    - Correspondence, 1881-1886; undated (Box 68)
      1881 F 3 to Godfrey Noyes
      Mr 15 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ap 30 to Mrs. Haworth
      Jl 3 to Mr. Hamilton
      Ag 1 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ag 17 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ag 20 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ag 21 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ag 23 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ag 25 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 3 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 27 to Tirzah C. Miller
      O 9 to Tirzah C. Miller
      to Harriet H. Skinner
      1882 F 1 to James B. Herrick
      F 10 to Harriet H. Skinner
      Ap 26 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 22 to Frank Wayland-Smith
      1883 Ja 16 to James B. Herrick
      Ja 28 to James B. Herrick
      F 8 to James B. Herrick
      F 8 to James B. Herrick?
      F 9 to James B. Herrick?
      Mr 3 to Harriet H. Skinner
      My 26 to Harriet H. Skinner
      1884 F to ?
      1885 My 5 to Tirzah C. Miller
      My 25 to Tirzah C. Miller
      undated 6 letters to Tirzah C. Miller
      undated 2 letters to James B. Herrick
      undated 2 letters to Charlotte [Charlotte M. Leonard?]
      undated 1 letter to Mrs. Joslyn
      undated 6 letters to unidentified recipients
      v.d. Home Talks (scrapbook) v. 1: #1-67
      Home Talks (scrapbook) v. 2 #68-183
    - Niagara Copybook (index pages only filmed), 1880-1882 (Box 68)
    - Writings, 1843-1885 (Box 69)
      Home Talks (scrapbook) v. 3: #184-
      Home Talks
      Portrait of J.H.N. by C.A. Miller (before 1840) (copy; original in KHC Collection)
      Engraving (portrait from Home talks)
      1881-1885 Niagara Journal and Stone Cottage Talks [recorded by Fanny M. Leonard]
      "Memoir of Hon. John Noyes"
    - Writings, 1843-1885 (Box 70)
      1843 "All Perfectionists ought ..." (with Battle- axe letter and letter by Alexander Wilder) (transferred from C.N. Robertson Coll.)
      N 23 to "Dear Friends" (transferred from C.N. Robertson Coll.)
      1851 Jl 1 "The rights of the human mind"
      Jl 7 "The surrender of our talents to God" (transferred from C.N. Robertson Coll.)
      1852 D 21 "Our victories"
      1853 Ja 22 "Labor and appetite" The Circular
      (F 9, 1853), p. 99
      1853 F 24 "Woman's rights"
      1864 Ap 10 "Evening conversation"
      1866 "The Kingdom of Heaven"
      1867 "Studies on the fingerboard"
      1867 F 26 "My marriage with Harriet A."
      1875 F 24 "Continence"
      1877 Ap 19 "A paper by Mr. Noyes"
      1879 N 4 "The future of stirpiculture"
      1880 Je 11 ["On free love"]
      1880 N 09 "J.H.N.'s Covenant of Peace"
      1881 F OS Introduction to THE STORY OF DANIEL HAYES CAPTIVITY
      1881 "Niagara Falls as international city"
      Mr "Mr. Noyes" justification of Winnie"
      1882 Ja 19 "Gog and Magog"
      Mr 21 "Mr. Noyes" first epistle to the Hebrews"
      N 10 Home talk
      N 15 "On multiplicity of crimes"
      1883 Ja 25 "Education: a morning talk"
      S 1 "The charitable and hopeful view of the social state of the Community"
      1884 Ag 22 "How the essay on scientific propagation came to be written and published" (copy; original in Huntington Library)
      S Note re: Tirzah C. Miller
      1885 "God's bullets"
      Mr 17 Evening talk
      Mr 30 "Word from Mr. Noyes to Pierre"
      Ag 13 "A talk to the young"
      1866-1867 Home talks
    - Writings, undated (Box 70)
      "Divinity of the will"
      "Dorothy Draggletail"
      "From Headquarters No. 1"
      Niagara Falls writings:
      J.H. Noyes to Mr. Porter "A study of the whirlpool"
      "Paying prospects of the new boat"
      "What reasons have we for believing that Niagara Falls will be a great city"
      "On possession of this house"
      "Sayings of J.H.N."
      "Pauls gospel" ["Boccaccio"]
      ["Mr. Noyes's talk"]
      "Steps of the ladder"
      "The way to take criticism" Miscellaneous fragments
    - Writings (oversize)
      - "The common chord of first, third, fifth and octave justified by the law of vibrations, and shown to be the rational origin of the common scale", undated (Oversize 7)
      - "Prolongation of life: recovery of youth" and "Self-help and self-protection", undated (Oversize 2)
    - Legal, Financial, 1844-1870; undated (Box 70)
      1844 F 26 Contract of partnership between John Humphrey Noyes, John R. Miller, George Washington Noyes, John L. Skinner
      1878 Je 21 Covenant with Tirzah C. Miller re: Edward P. Inslee
      1880 D 31 Articles of Agreement between John Humphrey Noyes and Oneida Community Ltd.
      "The law of ejectment"
      Stone Cottage property: statement
      Sketch of John Humphrey Noyes's editorial desk (copy; original in KHC Coll.)
      "Way marks in the life of J.H.N." (1862?)
      1870 N 24 First Children's Hour (with Harriet H. Skinner)
      Dartmouth Necrology
      Clippings: Obituaries
  - Noyes, John Humphrey (II), 1886-1928 (Box 71)
    1886 Niagara Diary
    1892 O 11 to Dorothy Barron
    1928 File of correspondence with Peter Stuck (Amana Society) re: reorganization into joint stock
  - Noyes, Miriam T. (Earl), 1877-1914 (Box 71)
    Sketchbook (copy; original in KHC Coll.)
    1877-1914 Family scrapbooks (copy)
    1896 D 26 to Dorothy Barron
    1898 N 24 to Dorothy Barron
  - Noyes, Pierrepont B., 1894-1951; undated (Box 71)
    1894 N 14 to Stephen R. Leonard (II) N 23 to Stephen R. Leonard (II)
    1909-1912 Correspondence with S.R. Leonard (II)
    1950 Ag 25 to Agents
    Ag 28 to friends (copy)
    undated "On the 1st of May
    71 Noyes, Polly
    1951 O 23 to Marcus L. Worden
  - Noyes, Rhoda Hero Burnham Dunn, 1915; undated (Box 71)
    1915 My 11 "Letter on theological subjects to F.W.
    Frankland from a granddaughter of the founder of the Oneida Community" (4 p.)
  - Noyes, Theodore R., 1863-1902; undated
    - Correspondence (Box 71)
      1863 D 14 to Arthur Towner
      1865 Ag 2 to George E. Cragin
      Ag 15 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1866 Ap 13 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ap 20 to Mary Louise Prindle
      My 18 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ag 7 to Tirzah C. Miller
      5 30 to Mary Louise Prindle
      N 25 to Alfred Barron
      1867 Ja 6 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Ja 27 to Mary Louise Prindle
      F 7 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Mr 2 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Mr 10 to Tirzah C. Miller
      My 8 to Mary Louise Prindle
      My 27 to George Washington Noyes
      Jl 8 to Mary Louise Prindle
      1868 F 12 to Beulah Hendee
      D 17 to Mr. Elliot
      1869 Mr 20 to David S. Wells, Commissioner of Revenue (copy)
      Ag 2 to G.F. Barker
      Ag 4 to G.F. Barker
      1870 Mr 21 to Mary Louise Prindle (1879?)
      1872 Ap 6 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 1 to Editor, Journal of Applied Chemistry
      O 5 Statement from Our Home Hygenic Institute
      1875 Mr 24 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ap 28 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1876 Je 30 to Epes Sargent
      Jl 17 to Epes Sargent
      Ag 7 to Mary Louise Prindle
      N 25 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1877 My 30 to James B. Herrick
      1878 My 9 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Je 27 to Harriet A. Noyes
      (with H.A.Noyes to T.R.Noyes)
      Jl 17 to J.J. Skinner
      1879 F 9 to John Humphrey Noyes
      F 14 to John Humphrey Noyes
      1880 S 19 to John Humphrey Noyes
      N 28 to Mary Louise Prindle
      1881 Mr 11 to James B. Herrick
      1884 S 21 to George Wallingford Noyes
      O 12 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1888 Mr 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
      189? to ?
      1891 S 13 to Anita Newcomb McGee (copy; original at Kinsey Institute)
      1892 Ap 15 to Anita Newcomb McGee (copy; original at Kinsey Institute)
      D 14 to Mary Louise Prindle
      1893 F 22 to William A. Hinds
      Ap 17 to William A. Hinds
      D 13 to William A. Hinds
      1894 Ap 17 to William A. Hinds
      N 16 to Stephen R. Leonard (II)
      D 15 to William A. Hinds
      D 18 to William A. Hinds
      1895 Ja 16 to William A. Hinds, Kinsley, and Kellog
      F 21 to William A. Hinds, Kinsley, and Kellog
      F 26 to William A. Hinds
      Ap 2 to Rose Wright Bryan
      Ap 2 to William A. Hinds
      Ap 24 to William A. Hinds
      1899 D 8 to William A. Hinds
      1901 Mr 9 to Dorothy Barron
      Ag 23 to Theodore R. Noyes from former O.C. member
      1902 F 19 to G.N. Miller
      Mr 2 to William A. Hinds
    - Writings (Box 71)
      "Report on nervous diseases in the Oneida Community"
      (copy) Medical Gazette 5:253-258 (1870)
      The Graphic (Je 21, 1876)
      Miscellaneous works: o Pencil rubbing. o Drawing of O.C. (copy) o Penmanship books (2) o Untitled play.
      Miscellaneous Yale College material
      Medical lectures, 1864-1865
      Notebook, 1864-1865
      Catalogue of Medical Institution of Yale College, 1864-65.
      Order of exercises at the Commencement (1867)
  - Noyes, Victor C., 1866-1875 (Box 71)
    1866 Ag 30 to Gerrit Smith (copy; original in Syracuse University's Gerrit Smith Coll.)
    1869 N 7 to Gerrit Smith (copy; original in Syracuse University's Gerrit Smith Coll.)
    1875 F 12 to Tirzah C. Miller
  - Olds, Charles, 1848-1886; undated (Box 72)
    1848 O 27 to Silas Howard (copy; original in Amherst College Library)
    1863 Je 7 to Silas Howard (copy; original in Amherst College Library)
    1871 Ap 27 to 'Dear Friends' (copy; original in Amherst College Library)
    undated poem (copy; original in Amherst College Library)
    [no year] My 1 to Silas Howard (copy; original in Amherst College Library)
    1867-1891 File of letters to Harriet Matthews
    1862-1873 File of letters to Harriet N. Olds
    1874-1878 File of letters to Harriet N. Olds
    1850-1852 Notebook
    1853-1855 Notebook
    1879 Notebook
    1863 Diary
    1886 Diary
    undated Business card
  - Olds, Harriet Noyes, 1862-1847; undated (Box 72)
    1862 Je 5 to Abigail Kellogg
    1875 O 5 to Harriet Matthews
    1874 Diary
    [no year] O 21 fragment
    Miscellaneous writings
  - Otis, Emily, 1857-1878; undated (Box 72)
    1857 Jl 17 from [?]
    1861 F 13 from Hannah Otis
    1864 N 2 to Beulah Hendee
    in Beulah Hendee file
    D 20 to Beulah Hendee
    1865 F to Beulah Hendee
    Mr 1 to Beulah Hendee
    Jl to Beulah Hendee
    1866 Ap 26 to Portia Underhill
    Ap 26 to Beulah Hendee
    1867 N 25 to Harriet N. Olds
    My 5 to Beulah Hendee
    1876 Ag 14 to Beulah Hendee
    D 4 to Harriet
    1877 Ap 12 to Beulah Hendee
    O 30 to Charles A. Cragin
    1878 Ja 4 from [?]
    undated to [?] (JHN? with a reply)
    undated Ag to Charles A. Cragin
  - Perry, William H., 1839; 1851 (Box 73)
    1839 Mr 21 to Jonathan Burt
    1851 Ap 7 to Marcus L. Worden
  - Pitt, Theodore L., 1878-1889; undated
    - Correspondence (Box 73)
      1878 Je 5 to James B. Herrick
      Je 12 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1879 My 21 note -- see Abel Easton file
      1880-1882 letters in John Humphrey Noyes's Niagara Copybook
      1881 D 4 to Alfred Barron
      o 15 to Alfred Barron
      1882 Ja 18 to Alfred Barron
      Mr 31 to Alfred Barron
      Ap 27 to Alfred Barron (2 letters)
      My 30 to Alfred Barron
      Jl 1 to Boston Post Master
      Jl 14 to Alfred Barron
      1886 Ap 30 "Interview with J.H. Noyes"
      1888 F 4 to George N. Miller (41 p.)
      1889 Ja 12 to Alfred Barron?
      undated to 'Dear Friends'
      Complex marriage hymn (copy)
      Statement about rumors
    - Writings (Box 73)
      "The Oneida Community: as it is now, and how it became so" Letter to the Editor, The Health Monthly (July, 1886) p. 10-
      "Koinonia: the socialism of Jesus" (18 p.)
      "The Parousia" (1910) (271 p. typescript)
      Niagara Falls "Review" Extra (N 4, 1887)
  - Pomeroy, Mary O., 1867-1868; undated (Box 73)
    [no year] Je 10 to Harriet Matthews
    undated Sat. to Harriet N. Olds
  - Prindle, Mary Louise, 1864-1909; undated (Box 73)
    1864 Ag 8 to Harriet N. Olds
    1867 Ja 4 to Theodore R. Noyes
    Mr 10 to Theodore R. Noyes
    My 2 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    My 21 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1868 Ja to Tirzah C. Miller
    Mr 18 to Stephen R. Leonard (with S.R. Leonard to C.M. Leonard)
    1869 Ja 11 to John Humphrey Noyes
    F 5 to Theodore R. Noyes
    Ag 27 to Tirzah C. Miller
    S 3 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    S 30 to Tirzah C. Miller
    O 28 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1870 Jl 20 to Tirzah C. Miller
    S 5 to Tirzah C. Miller
    N 10 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1871 F 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1875 F 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1877 Mr 12 to Harriet N. Olds
    Mr 30 to Harriet N. Olds
    Jl 4 to William A. Hinds
    1878 Jl 1 to Theodore R. Noyes
    Jl 19 to John Humphrey Noyes
    Jl 20 to John Humphrey Noyes
    Ag 5 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    Ag 8 to Charlotte M. Leonard
    1879 F 5 to Beulah Hendee
    Ap 12 to G.N. Miller
    Ap 24 to Aunt Helen
    My 8 to Harriet H. Skinner
    1880 Ap 1 to Tirzah C. Miller (2 letters)
    S 25 to Tirzah C. Miller in G.N. Miller file (10-22-80)
    O 4 to Tirzah C. Miller
    O 25 to Tirzah C. Miller
    N 4 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1882 O 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
    N 16 to Beulah Hendee
    N 28 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1883 Ja 16 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Ja 20 to 'Friend'
    F 1 to Mr. H.
    F 7 to Charlotte N. Leonard
    Mr 1 to James B. Herrick
    1884 N to James B. Herrick
    N 23 to John Humphrey Noyes (with John Humphrey Noyes's reply & note to William A. Hinds)
    N 27 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1887 N 15 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1893 Ja 25 to ?
    F 6 to ?
    1895 Ja 30 to Tirzah C. Miller Herrick (extract)
    1896 Ja 9 to George Wallingford Noyes
    1906 Je 10 to O.C.L. Directors
    1907 Je 14 to Pierrepont B. Noyes
    1909 F 22 to G.N. Miller
    undated 2 letters to John Humphrey Noyes
    undated 2 letters to Theodore R. Noyes
    undated 3 letters to Tirzah C. Miller
    undated 2 letter to James B. Herrick
  - Ransom, Charles A., 1876-1877 (Box 73)
    1876 O 12 to Harriet H. Skinner
    1877 Ja 23 to Tirzah C. Miller
  - Reeve, Gaylord, 1878-1880; undated (Box 73)
    1878 Ap 1 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1880 Ap 3 to Charlotte M. Leonard?
    1880 Je 26 to Charlotte N. Leonard
    N 10 to Lily Cragin
    undated to Emily Otis
  - Reeve, Martha, 1874-1879; diary (Box 73)
  - Reid, Charlotte A., 1876-1879 (Box 73)
    1876 O 28 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1878 My 12 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Je 25 to Mary Louise Prindle
    O 30 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1879 Ja 6 to Mary Louise Prindle
  - Reynolds, James, 1843-1870 (Box 73)
    File of 22 letters to James Reynolds from family
  - Richards, Charles, 1915 (Box 73)
    "Eugenics tried by Oneida Community" (clipping)
  - Robinson, Annie, undated (Box 73)
    Biographical information
  - Sears, Ann Cooley, 1852; 1855 (Box 73)
    1852 F 22 to 'Friends in Putney'
    1855 My 2 to Marcus L. Worden
  - Sears, John, 1877-1880; undated (Box 73)
    1877 My 23 to Beulah Hendee
    Je 5 to Beulah Hendee
    Jl 6 to Beulah Hendee
    1878 5 29 to Beulah Hendee
    O 9 to Beulah Hendee
    O 14 to Beulah Hendee
    N 3 to Beulah Hendee
    N 6 to Beulah Hendee
    N 30 to Beulah Hendee
    D 6 to Beulah Hendee
    D 18 to Beulah Hendee
    D 19 to Beulah Hendee
    1879 Ja 12 to Beulah Hendee
    Ja 17 to Beulah Hendee
    F 4 to Beulah Hendee
    F 10 to Beulah Hendee
    F 12 to Beulah Hendee
    F 18 to Beulah Hendee
    F 22 to Beulah Hendee
    F 28 to Beulah Hendee
    Mr 3 to Beulah Hendee
    Mr 9 to Beulah Hendee
    Mr 11 to Beulah Hendee
    Ap 10 to Beulah Hendee
    My 10 to Beulah Hendee
    My 25 to Beulah Hendee
    Je 9 to Beulah Hendee
    1880 Ja 21 to Beulah Hendee
    [no year] D 22 to Beulah Hendee
  - Seymour, Chloe, 1869; undated (Box 73)
    1869 Ja 31 to Harriet N. Olds
    undated to Harriet N. Olds
  - Seymour, Henry J., 1851-1903; undated (Box 73)
    1851 Mr 6 to Marcus L. Worden
    1867 O 10 to Woolworth
    1878 Jl 26 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1888 F 11 to W.G. Kelly (16 p. letter with extracts of a second letter)
    F 26 to James B. Herrick
    Mr 4 to James B. Herrick
    1903 Mr 22 to Elbert Hubbard (copy)
    undated to Manlius Friends
  - Seymour, Tryphena, 1861-1862 (Box 73)
    1861 Ja 1 to Marcus L. Worden
    N 7 to Marcus L. Worden
    D 1 to Marcus L. Worden
    D 18 to Marcus L. Worden
    1862 Ja 19 to Marcus L. Worden
    F 6 to Marcus L. Worden
  - Sibley, Phoebe, 1867; 1879 (Box 73)
    1879 F 9 to Naomi Howard (copy; original in Amherst College Library)
  - Skinner Family, undated (Box 74)
    1 folder miscellaneous material
  - Skinner, Harriet H., 1847-1890; undated (Box 74)
    - Correspondence
      Je 28 to Lovett (copy; original in Vermont Historical Soc.?)
      1848 Ja 27 to Lovett--see Harriet A. Noyes file
      1849 F 22 to Marcus L. Worden--in Mary E. Cragin file
      1890 Ag 12 to Theodore Skinner
      File of letters to Tirzah C. Miller
      File of letters to Harriet N. Olds, Beulah Hendee, Alfred Barron, E.H., Hamilton, Mrs. Dunn, Mary J. Nead, J.L. Skinner
      File of letters to stirpicults (Humphrey, Gertrude, George)
      File of letters to John Humphrey Noyes and Harriet A. Noyes
      File of letters to Charlotte M. Leonard
      File of letters to Mary Louise Prindle
      File of letters to James B. Herrick
      File of letters to Marcus L. Worden
      Unidentified fragments
    - Writings
      Genealogical account
  - Skinner, John L., 1820-1877 (Box 74)
    - Correspondence
      182- to Chloe Skinner
      1821 D 2 to Chloe Skinner
      1822 A 18 to Avery Skinner
      1823 My 19 to Chloe Skinner
      1833 O 1 to Albert G. Skinner
      1851 Ja 30 to Marcus L. Worden
      F 8 to Marcus L. Worden
      F 21 to Marcus L. Worden
      Ap 4 to Marcus L. Worden
      Ap 10 to Marcus L. Worden
      Ap 17 to Marcus L. Worden
      1852 Je 13 to Marcus L. Worden
      1854 Je 8 to Marcus L. Worden
      1865 My 1 to Harriet Matthews
      1871 D 18 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1875-1878 File of letters to E.A. Wallbridge, Ezra Yoder, Lucy Haworth
      1873-1879 File of E.A. Wallbridge's letters to J.L. Skinner
      1876 Ag 15 to Harriet Matthews
      1877 Mr 26 to Benjamin Ellis
    - Writings
      1820-1838 Early verse & misc. writings
      1834-1838 Journal (copy)
      1835-1837 Journal
      1838-1841 Journal
      1840? Journal
      1840? "Battle-axism" Journal
      1852-1855 Journal o 1855 Journal
      1858-1865 Diary fragments
      1866 Journal
      1863 "Progress in the Community"
  - Skinner, Joseph J., 1865-1902 (Box 74)
    1865 Ja 13 poem addressed to Tirzah C. Miller
    1869 Mr 14 to James B. Herrick
    1870 Ja 24 to James B. Herrick
    1873-1875 Journal (copy)
    1879 Ag 23 Francis A. Walker telegram to J.J.S.
    Ag 27 Stanley Rule & Level Co. to J.J.S.
    1881 Ap 15 William Parker telegram to J.J.S.
    1895-1902 File of 18 letters to William A. Hinds
    Writings: o v.d. Miscellaneous offprints of scientific papers o 1873 Record of J.J. Skinner after leaving O.C. (copy) [misidentified as Theodore Skinner]
  - Skinner, Theodore H., 1875-1897 (Box 74)
    1875-1883 Diary
    1883 Mr 4 to Joseph J. Skinner
    1896 F 21 to William A. Hinds
    1897 F 19 to William A. Hinds
    F 19 to Oneida Community Ltd.
  - Skinner, Viola, 1928; 1942 (Box 74)
    1928 N 15 to Hope E. Allen
    1942 "Viola and Theodore...
  - Smith, D. Edson, 1900-1909 (Box 75)
    File of 6 letters to William A. Hinds
  - Smith, E. Deming, 1887-1907 (Box 75)
    1887 5 4 to George
    1887-1908 File of 5 letters to William A. Hinds
    1902-1907 File of letters to Mrs. H. G. Allen
  - Smith, Sarah Frances, 1870-1871; undated (Box 75)
    1870 Ap 28 to Harriet
    Jl 14 to Harriet N. Olds
    S 13 to Harriet N. Olds
    S 20 to Harriet N. Olds
    O 6 to Harriet N. Olds
    1871 Ja 8 to Harriet N. Olds
    Ap 20 to Harriet N. Olds
    S 19 to Libbie Kellogg
  - Stillman, E.A., 1837 (Box 75)
    O 15 to John Humphrey Noyes
  - Story, S. A., 1878-1890 (Box 75)
    1880 My 12 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1882 Ag 13 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1887 O 4 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1890 Ag 22 to Maria Barron
  - Sweet, Martin P., 1843 (Box 75)
    F 8 to Jonathan Burt
  - Thacker, Henry, 1880 (Box 75)
    Ag 15 to James B. Herrick
  - Thayer, Henry W., 1850 (Box 75)
    N 13 to Marcus L. Worden
  - Thayer, Lucy Ann, 1867-1880; undated (Box 75)
    v.d. File of 24 letters to Marcus L. Worden
    1867 Je 20 to Silas and Naomi Howard (copy; original in Amherst College Library)
    1867 Jl 16 to Harriet
    1871 Ja 29 to Naomi Howard (copy; original in Amherst College Library)
    Ap 23 to Naomi Howard (copy; original in Amherst College Library)
    1877 F 9 to Naomi Howard (copy; original in Amherst College Library)
    1878 My 20 to Mary
    1880 D 2 to James B. Herrick
  - Tinsley, William, See Barron, Maria: letter to Dorothy Barron Leonard (Ja 18, 1910)
  - Towner, James W., 1874-1909